-泰迪  -太好了
-Teddy. -Great!
泰迪  我要和你说...
Teddy, I've got to talk...
噢  别开玩笑了  到底怎么了
Oh... you're kidding. Then what happened?
哇
Wow.
稍等  又有别的电话打进来了
Hold on. I'm getting another call.
玩真的
Really?
是的
Really.
再等下  一会我再给你回电话
Hold on. I've got to call you back.
-干吗  -你说干什么
-What? -What?
我刚接到话费账单
I just opened up the phone bill.
你的话费透支了九十美元
You are $90 over your texting limit.
看你怎么解释这件事
What have you got to say about that?
“我爱你  老爹”
"I love you, daddy"?
别这样  泰迪  你也太没有责任心了
Come on, Teddy, this is so irresponsible.
我对你抱有很大期望的
I expect more from you.
等下  我先发条短信
Hold on. I'm getting a text.
算了  你发不了了
No, you're not,
因为我要把你的手机没收
'cause I'm taking your phone away.
什么  你不能这样对我
What? No, you can't do that.
没收我的手机犹如没收你的披萨
Taking away my phone would be like taking away your pizza.
你居然为了你的破手机
You're fighting for your phone.
而暗指我很胖
By calling me fat?
那个  我只是很生气
Well, I'm just really mad.
我爱你  老爹
I love you, daddy.
和你说下  如果想拿回你的手机
I'll tell you what... You'll get your phone back.
-就先凑齐九十块大洋  -这太不公平了
-When you come up with 90 bucks. -That's so unfair.
嘿  老爸
Hey dad.
我和你说点儿事
Uh, I gotta tell you something.
又咋了
What?
那个  在我把车开进车库时
Well, I was pulling into the garage.
好像蹭到了您的战车
And I kind of scraped the bug truck.
上面的字从“鲍勃到  臭虫害虫灭光光”
Instead of "Bob's bugs be gone"
变成了“罗伯来  地毯毛毯跑光光”
it now says "Rob's rugs be gone."
PJ
P.J.!
什么事  老爸
Yeah, dad?
尽量小心点可以吗
Try and be more careful.
就完了  他得到了一句勉励的话
That's it? He gets "try and be more careful"
而我得到的却是手机没收  太没天理了
and I get my phone taken away? Unbelievable!
哇  她还真是棘手  是吧罗伯
Whoa. She's a handful, eh, Rob?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E02  Something's Fishy
嘿  同志们  一会见
Hey, guys, see you later.
你要带查莉出去吗
Are you taking Charlie somewhere?
是的  去商场  我们要购物去
Yes, to the mall. We're going to go shopping.
为什么去购物
Shopping for what?
泡妞
Girls.
她们就是无法抗拒我们的可爱小妹妹
They just can't resist our adorable little sister.
你居然用我们的小妹来做诱饵
I can't believe you'd use Charlie as girl bait.
哦算了  任他去吧
Oh, let him do it.
对于一个没有魅力与气质的人来说
Without charm or personality,
也就只能玩这小把戏
it's his only play.
我谢你
Thank you.
好吧  但是记住在三点之前把查莉送回来
All right, just have Charlie back by 3:00.
我要带她去一个生日聚会  在奥托游乐场
I'm taking her to a birthday party at Otto's grotto.
没问题  我们一会儿就回来
Oh, no problem. Shouldn't take long.
嘿  查莉  说我刚教给你的那句
Hey, Charlie, say that thing I taught you.
我耐PJ
I wuv P.J.
“耐”  她能说“爱”了
"Wuv"? She can say "love."
是啊  但是“耐”可以帮我钓到更多的女生
I know, but "wuv" gets me way more girls.
嘿宝贝
Hey honey.
-嘿  -怎么了
-Hey. -What's wrong?
没人和我玩网球电子游戏
Nobody to play video tennis with.
我的朋友们不是在做作业
All my friends are doing homework.
就是在和家人共度美好时光
Or spending time with their families...
你们这帮衰人
Losers.
我来和你玩
I'll play with you.
我还是去看书吧
I think I'll go read a book.
你宁愿去看书
You'd rather read a book.
也不愿意和你老妈我玩电子游戏
Than play video games with your mom?
是啊  说的没错
Yeah, you're right.
我还是去小睡一觉吧
I'm gonna go take a nap.
盖比  我以前玩过这东西
Gabe, I've played video games before.
我知道我在干嘛
I know what I'm doing.
那是电视遥控器  老妈
Mom, that's the tv remote.
我正想把它拿开
Which I'm moving out of the way.
便于我拿起游戏控制器
So that I can pick up a controller.
好了  快给老娘我整好  电玩小子
All right, serve it up, Sonny boy.
好吧
Fine.
这并不是那么的有趣
This won't be any fun.
好了  准备好了吗
Okay, are you ready?
放马过来吧
Go for it.
哇  这确实比我想的要有趣多了
Wow, this might be more fun than I thought.
查莉呢  查莉去哪了
Where's Charlie? Where'd Charlie go?
噢  她在这里呢  在这呢
Oh, there she is. There she is.
好啊  好啊  好啊
Yeah yeah yeah.
噢  我们也许应该把这放回去
Oh, wow. Maybe we should put that back.
我的
Mine.
好了  少一个两个  他们应该不会知道的
Well, they probably won't miss one ball.
我每天晚上都会清点个数
I count every ball every night!
你能帮我拉上吗
Can you zip me up?
这个还是算了
No. No, thank you.
以前经常有个女孩来扮演美人鱼的
The girl that usually plays the mermaid...
现在她走了
she quit on me.
她现在在汉克的汉堡包店装扮成泡菜
She's now the Pickle at hamburger Hank's.
还是你了解她
Well, you knew her when.
那个汉克快把我逼疯了
That Hank is killing me.
他是个守财奴  吝啬鬼
With his fancy minimum wage.
真不敢相信我要这么说
I can't believe I'm about to say this,
我来做这份工作怎么样
but I could use a job.
好吧  先别急
Okay, slow it down.
要想在奥托游乐场工作需要满足三条要求
It takes three things to work at Otto's grotto.
-第一  必须年满十六岁  -满足
-One... you gotta be 16. -I am.
第二  很擅长和孩子打交道
Two... you gotta be good with kids,
基本上就是善于和他们的呕吐物打交道
which basically means willing to clean up their puke.
我有气无力的回答  “满足”
"I am," she said less excitedly.
最后  最重要的一点
And most important,
你要会说海之语
you gotta speak the language of the sea.
海什么
The what?
比如“不要那么易怒  孩子们
Like "don't be crabby, kids.
注：crabby：易怒 crab：螃蟹
我们会很快乐的”什么的
We're gonna have a whale of a time. " Stuff like that.
注：whale of time 玩的很开心  whale:鲸鱼
那是我们吸引孩子的手段
It's our hook.
哇  我又说了一遍
Whoa, I just did it again!
注：clam up:闭口不谈  clam：蛤蜊
好了  别担心  我不会对你这么说的
Yeah, well, don't worry. I won't clam up on you.
不急  你早晚会说的
Well, you'll work on it.
-你什么时候可以来上班  -越快越好
-When can you start? -The sooner the baiter.
你首次清理的呕吐物  很可能是我的
The first puke you clean up may be mine.
好了  盖比  你觉着如何
Okay, Gabe, what do you think?
扣上  还是敞开
Buttoned? Unbuttoned?
敞开  让那四根胸毛来透透气
Unbuttoned... give those four chest hairs a chance to breathe.
这么说来  你邀请了个女孩来咱家
So you got a girl coming over?
是的  她叫凯拉  商场遇见的
Yep, her name is Kayla. I met her at the mall.
是查莉帮你钓到的女生
Charlie got you a girl?
是啊  效果奇佳啊
Yeah, worked like a charm...
除了查莉自己有点困惑
Well, except Charlie got a little confused.
她把“我耐PJ”
Instead of saying "I wuv P.J."
说成了“我耐便便”
She said, "I wuv poopy."
我觉着查莉知道自己在说什么
I think Charlie knew what she was saying.
但是我马上扭转了颓势
Yeah, but I totally saved it.
我告诉凯拉我的昵称叫便便
I told Kayla my nickname was poopy.
凯拉和便便
Kayla and poopy...
真是一段千年佳话啊  老兄
Many years of happiness, sir.
别掉链子啊  帅哥  展现你的魅力吧
Come on, boys, work your magic.
-嗨  凯拉  -嗨
-Hi Kayla. -Hi.
-这是我弟弟  盖比  -噢  天啊
-This is my brother Gabe. -Ooh ooh ooh!
查莉  我的小心肝
Charlie, there's my little sweetie.
快让我抱抱
Hi. Come here.
祝你好运  便便
Have fun, poopy.
你想去楼下玩玩吗
So do you want to hang out downstairs?
我有个更好的注意
I have an even better idea.
灰烬  灰烬  我们都倒下
Ashes ashes, we all fall down.
哦天啊  你太棒了
Oh my goodne, you're so good.
好了  谁想玩躲猫猫
Okay, who wants to play peek-a-boo?
-谁想玩躲猫猫  -其实
-Who wants to play peek-a-boo? -Actually,
查莉现在该去睡觉了
Charlie has to take her nap right now.
噢
Oh.
好吧  那我也去睡会
Well, I guess I'll be going.
什么
Really?
我还以为可以有点独处的时间
I thought we could have some Kayla and poopy time.
好吧  也许下次可以
Yeah, well, maybe next time.
但这次玩得真尽兴
But this was a really good playdate.
是啊
I guess, yeah.
-再见了  查莉  -再见
-Bye, Charlie. -Goodbye-bye.
谁将得到一个香吻  没错就是你
Who's gonna get a big kiss? I'm going in.
-哈  -妈
-Ha! -Mom.
-哈  -爸
-Ha! -Dad!
-哈  -妈
-Ha! -Mom.
-哈  -爸
-Ha! -Dad!
哈
Ha!
您能歇歇吗
Can you please make it stop?
你搞什么
What are you doing?
练习网球电子游戏  盖比今天把我虐了
Practicing video tennis. Gabe crushed me today.
你知道现在已经十一点了吗
You know, it's about 11:00.
知道  可老娘我可不喜欢失败的滋味
Yeah, well, mama don't like to lose.
以前这里是不是有盏台灯
Didn't we used to have a lamp here?
绝对没有
I don't think so.
老爸  把她带走吧  我明天还要工作
Dad, get her out of here. I have work tomorrow.
你要去上班
You got a job?
是啊  我现在是奥托游乐场的美人鱼
Yeah, I am the puke-cleaning mermaid
专门清理呕吐物
at Otto's grotto.
但如果你把手机还给我  我立马辞职
But of course if you give me my phone back I can still quit.
记住一定要带手套
Be sure and wear gloves.
哈  哈
Ha! Ha!
好了  睡觉去吧
All right, let's go.
快点  给我球拍
Come on, give me the controller.
现在不是时候  老娘我状态正佳
Not now. Mama's in the zone.
是啊  老娘可从来找不到状态
Yeah, mama doesn't know where the zone is.
嘿
Hey.
太好了  很准时啊
Oh good. You're right on time.
是啊  毕竟这是我第一天上班
Yeah, well, it's my first day.
我可不想让你在这里痛苦地挣扎着
I didn't want to leave you floundering.
注:floundering:挣扎  flounder：川鲽（一种比目鱼）
我的美人鱼套装呢
So where's my mermaid suit?
没有  那是为女生派对准备的
No, that was for a girls' party.
今天是男生派对
Today you are working a boys' party.
他们可不喜欢美人鱼
They don't like mermaids.
好吧  那他们喜欢什么
All right, so what do they like?
嘿  嘿  住手  奥利章鱼可不是皮纳塔
Hey hey, stop that. Ollie octopus is not a pinata.
（注：皮纳塔是挂起来让小孩子挥棒子打的一种东西，打破了就有糖果掉出来 ）
我知道  但是皮纳塔很好玩
I know. Pinatas are fun.
好了  小孔雀鱼们  带好你们自己的鞋
Okay, guppies, grab your shoes...
或者随手找双鞋
Or any shoes.
去外面找你们的父母
And join your parents outside.
嘿  你来最后锁门  好吧
Hey, lock up for me, will you?
等下  什么
Wait, what?
还有别忘了清点小球的数量
And don't forget to count the balls.
好了  你们刚听见那个人说的了
All right, you heard the man.
全都出去
Everybody out.
快看啊
Na na!
来拿啊
你等着  我的触手迟早会抓到你的
Just wait till I get my tentacles on you.
嘿  我卡里面了
Hey, I'm stuck.
帅哥帮帮我吧
Could you help me?
没门
No.
有人吗
Hello?
Anybody?
秋命啊
Kelp.
注：kelp：海藻
我打的越来越好了  是不是
Uh! I'm getting better, aren't I?
是啊  老妈
Yeah, mom.
这次只是六比一惨败
That time you only lost 6-1.
嘿  嘿  你要干嘛
Hey hey, excuse me, what are you doing?
我要复习历史了  明天有考试
I have to study for my history test tomorrow.
快把你的书放下  拿起游戏控制器
Put that book down and pick up the controller.
爸  老妈不让我学习
Dad, mom won't let me do my homework.
和我打完了你再学
You can do it when you finish playing.
真是纠结啊
I am so confused.
好吧  随便你
Fine. You know what?
写你的白痴作业吧
Finish your stupid homework.
等你理清楚什么才是最重要的后  再叫我吧
Call me when you get your priorities straight.
老爸  老爸  她完全失去理性了
Dad, dad, she's out of control.
你必须去找她谈谈心
You have to talk to her.
别傻了  你觉着她能听我的吗
Why? Because when I tell her to do things, she does them?
你注没注意过
Haven't you been paying attention.
解决问题的方法就近在眼前
To the way things work around here?
是吗  那我应该怎么做
Well, what am I supposed to do?
很简单  下次和她玩的时候  让她赢
Well, it's easy. Next time you play her, you let her win.
让她赢
Let her win?
你看见过她玩的吗
Have you ever seen her play?
我实在是质疑这个方法的可行性
I'm not even sure that's possible.
我敢肯定你会想出办法的
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
好了  快去复习功课吧
All right, come on, get over there and study for your test.
噢  考试是我瞎说的  就为了能摆脱她
Oh, I made that test up just to get rid of her.
-你想玩玩吗  -好啊
-You want to play? -Yeah, sure.
嘿凯拉  我们是要去野餐吗
Hey Kayla. Are we going on a picnic?
猜对了
Yes, we are.
我带了动物饼干  果汁
I have animal crackers, juice boxes.
还有切成星状的花生酱果酱三明治
And pb&j sandwiches cut into the shapes of stars.
哇  全是我爱吃的
Wow, all my favorites.
对不起  我是带给查莉的  傻瓜
No, I brought them for Charlie, silly.
那个  查莉不在家  妈妈带她去操场了
Well, Charlie's not here. Mom took her to the playground.
噢
Oh.
好吧  那咱们去那里找他们
Well, let's go meet them there.
告诉你吧  我开始在想
You know what? I'm starting to think.
你是不是更想和查莉在一起  而不是我
That you'd rather spend time with Charlie than with me.
什么
What?
别瞎说了
That's crazy.
你是不是在吃一个两岁小孩的醋
Are you really jealous of a two-year-old?
像你这样的一个帅哥
How can a hot guy like you.
怎能如此缺乏自信呢
Be so insecure?
-好了  感觉好多了  -是啊
-Okay, I'm feeling a little better. -Yeah.
“帅哥”那部分说的是实在精彩
The "hot guy" part really helped.
有人吗  泰迪
Hello? Teddy!
这里呢
In here.
什么...
What...?
你的第一天过得如何啊
So how was your first day?
把我弄出去  我卡住了
Get me out of here. I'm stuck.
好吧
Okay, all right.
别慌  我马上把你弄出去
Don't worry. I'm coming in after you.
哦天啊
Oh, man, wow.
知道吗  如果我没有话费限制
You know, if I had unlimited texting,
这就不会发生了
this wouldn't have happened.
好了  我试着把你推出去
Okay, I'm gonna try and push you out, okay?
使劲推啊
Now try pulling.
哇  你猜怎么着
Wow, you know what?
你像楔子一样卡死了  泰迪
You're really wedged in there, Teddy.
好了  我这就去找人...寻求帮助
All right, okay, I'm gonna... I'm gonna go for help.
惨了
Uh-oh.
-呵  -呃
-Huh! -Ugh!
好了  老妈  又是一记漂亮的击球
Well, another good shot, mom.
那是表扬我呢吗  因为你被我秒杀了
Is that a bell I hear? 'Cause you just got schooled.
你是在和我挑衅吗
Are you trash-talking me?
被吓到了吗  不敢了吗
What's the matter? Can't take it?
快回家找妈妈哭去吧
Gonna run home crying to your mommy?
你就是我妈
You are my mommy.
而你是我的手下败将
And you are my loser!
够了  够了  老妈
That's it. That's it, mom.
现在我玩真的了
Now I'm playing for real.
-那就让我看看  -好了  准备受死吧
-Let's do this. -Okay, let's to this.
你是从哪学的那招
Where did you learn how to do that?
我在网上找到了作弊器
I found some cheats on the Internet.
你是不是以为我不知道有作弊器啊
Didn't think I knew about cheats, did ya?
我以为你不知道有互联网
I didn't think you knew about the Internet.
老爸  你干吗老用屁股撞这管道啊
Dad, why are you banging your butt against the tube?
我在试着用屁股往家里打电话
I'm trying to butt-dial the house.
我把它设在了快拨一号键上
It's number one on the speed-dial,
所以应该不会太困难
so it should be easy.
拉尔夫披萨店
<i>Ralph's pizza.</i>
还是老几样  是吧鲍伯
<i>You want your usual,</i> <i>bobby?</i>
应该是快拨二号键
The house is on speed-dial two.
-老妈  接电话  -你去接
-Mom, phone. -You get it.
我不去  你去
No, you get it.
嗨呦
Hi-yo.
查莉  查莉  我是爸爸啊  宝贝
Charlie, Charlie, it's daddy, honey.
听着  去告诉你妈妈我们卡在管道里了
Listen, go tell your mother we're stuck in a tube.
在一个游乐场  这地方叫什么
At that kids' place at the mall. What's the name of this place?
爸  她才两岁
Dad, she's two.
说得好
Good point.
查莉  去找你妈妈
Charlie, go get your mommy.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
干得好  老爸
Good going, dad.
卡在这里的又不是我
I'm not the one who got stuck in a tube.
好吧  总之我不是第一个
Well, I'm not the first one anyway.
不  这都怪你  要不是为了还清账单
No, this is all your fault. If it wasn't for you,
我才不会来找这白痴工作
I wouldn't even need this stupid job.
嘿  你才是那个透支话费的人
Hey, you're the one who went over her texting minutes.
事出必有因
Actions do have consequences.
PJ怎么就没事
Not for P.J.
就好像给我定制了另一套标准
It's like you hold me to a totally different standard.
没错  我对你是有所不同
Yeah, I treat you differently.
但这是为什么啊
But why?
听着  泰迪  这不是关于PJ
Look, Teddy, this isn't about P.J.
这全是关于你
This is about you.
我对你抱有很大的期望
I have high expectations.
所以我才会对你严格要求
That's why I'm tough on you.
老爸  这太不公平了
Dad, that's not fair.
噢  宝贝  听着
Oh, honey, look,
我为你树立高标准严要求
I hold you to a high standard.
因为你是个能干大事的人
Because you are capable of great things.
真的
I am?
那个  是在将来
Well, in the future.
今天你只是被章鱼套装
Today you were defeated by an octopus costume.
和塑料管道打败了的悲剧女
And a plastic tube.
谢谢  老爸
Thanks, daddy.
什么声音
What was that?
声音像是...
That sounded like...
天啊
Whoa!
疼啊
Ow!
你俩在这里鏖战多久了
How long have you two been down here?
安静
Quiet!
我曾尝试往家里打电话
I tried calling the house.
有人注意听吗  是个紧急呼救电话
In case anyone is interested, it was an emergency.
接我一球
Take that!
-不不不  不要啊  -怎么回事
-No no no no no! -What happened?
噢  这个吗  这是为了你们好
Oh, this? This is for your own good.
可是  我们已经玩了六个小时了
Well, we've been playing for six hours.
我都快赢了
I was about to win.
是我快赢了
<i>I</i> was about to win.
好了  现在这是个迷了
Well, now we'll never know,
因为我要把这没收
because I'm taking this
放在一个高到你们够不到的架子上
and putting it on a high shelf.
我有点困惑  也许他是对的
I don't know, man. Maybe he's right.
也许我们是玩得疯了点
Maybe we did get a little crazy.
是啊  还记得我朋友杰克吗
Yeah. You know my friend Jake?
他家里也有这游戏
He has the same game at his house.
算了  现在太晚了
Nah, it's really late.
我知道他们把备用钥匙藏哪了
I know where they hide the spare key.
车里见
Meet you in the car.
嘿  凯拉  我是PJ
Hey, Kayla, it's P.J.
这好像是第五条留言了  你在哪里
It's, like, my fifth message. Where are you?
-她在厨房呢  -什么
-She's in the kitchen. -What?
这到底怎么回事
What is going on in here?
我可以解释的
I can explain.
-便便  我  -别叫我便便
-Poopy, I... -Don't you "poopy" me.
其实  事情不是像这样的
You know, it's not what it looks like.
是吗  但看起来就是这样的
Really? Because it looks like.
你居然背着我来和查莉玩
You're having a playdate behind my back.
对不起  但是...查莉真的是太可爱了
I'm sorry, but it's... Charlie is so cute.
然后就一发不可收拾了
And then one thing led to another...
算了  也许你离开对我们大家都好
No, I think it would be best for everyone if you left.
查莉  别让他这么对我
Charlie, don't let him do this.
帮我说句好话
Say something.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
你怎么能够这样对我
How could you?
我的错
I sorry.
噢  真是拿你没办法
Oh, I can't stay mad at you.
我耐PJ
I wuv P.J.
留着到商场再说吧  我们明天卷土重来
Save it for the mall. We're going back tomorrow.
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie,
我是你老爸  我今天为泰迪带班
it's your dad here. I'm filling in for Teddy.
因为她要为新工作做准备了
Because she's getting ready for her new job.
她现在在汉克汉堡包店工作
She's working over at hamburger Hank's now,
不会再有那傻不啦叽的章鱼套装了
so no more silly octopus costumes for her.
老爸  我准备好了  能走了吗
<i>Dad, I'm ready.</i> <i>Can we go?</i>
你想和你小妹妹说点什么吗
You want to say something to your little sister?
别  算了
No no.
不要透支你的话费
Don't ever go over your texting limit.
除非你想最后像我一样...
Unless you want to end up like me...
会跳舞的热狗
A dancing hot dog.
祝你好运喽  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
引以为戒
What she said.
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
我好像丢了某样东西
I'm missing a few things.
那个球坑好像变轻了
The ball pit was a little light.
你真的数了
You really count?
没错  我真的会数
Yes, I really count.
如果不去数它  你可不会成为丹佛市的
You don't become a #4 kids' entertainment purveyor.
第四个儿童娱乐承办商
In the Denver Metro area without counting!
好吧  可我们没有球
All right, well, we don't have any balls.
哦是吗
Oh really?
但是我注意到你的小妹妹
'Cause, see, I noticed that your little sister.
手脚并不是很干净
Had some sticky fingers.
好吧  我去问问
Fine. I'll ask.
查莉
Charlie,
你知道什么关于那些小球的事情吗
do you know anything about some missing balls?
还有吗  查莉
Is that it, Charlie?